It's 'cause we're from the same camp, duh!
Camp...?
Like the ones you see in sci-fi shows.
We're all guinea pigs used
for Prime Rights research.
Guinea pigs...? What are you talking about?
You dunno the half of Prime Rights.
It's an invention of human greed
on a whole 'nother level.
We're nothing but failed mediums
housing that greed.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Failures?
Let's just say they used whatever means
to force us into gaining Prime Rights.
Forced...?
Hang on a sec...
Omi lost hearing in his right ear,
and Sensei lost his right eyesight.
Of course!
They sacrificed crucial body parts
because they were forced to!
Anyone with Prime Rights
prior to Tasuketsu...
came from this "camp"!
We're failures who couldn't yield
the desired outcome of experiments.
Meaning the Emperor was
the only "success" of the bunch!
Success? Failures? What "camp"?
And why were Omi and the others there?
I'm sure you have a boatload of questions.
Tell ya what!
How 'bout I give you some information,
and you give me Omi-kun?
N-No way I could—
Sane, let's take it.
Omi in exchange for juicy info? Let's do it!
What?! Ryuta, are you cra—
If it's me you're worried 'bout, I'm fine!
...Okay.
Then it's a deal!
Is there a way to defeat the Emperor?
Yup! And it's much easier with Omi-kun.
But I won't tell you anything beyond that!
Why not recruit the owner of the
Obedience Right? Isn't that the strongest?
They're dead. Omi-kun's
the strongest of us alive.
Dead...?! Do you know where the Emperor is?
We have plenty of time to look for them.
Welp! I'm afraid that's all I can share.
Good for you guys Mido
wasn't the one to come here.
Is he really that dangerous?
We do have different end goals, after all.
End...?
Mido's end goal is to annihilate
the entire human race besides himself.
My goal is to annihilate the entire
human race including myself.
"Zero" and "one"...
How close, yet so far apart.
What?!
Including yourself?!
Sure! Why be alive?
It's no use.
Nothing in this world matters.
Same goes for you guys.
If you survive, then what?
You live, reproduce, and die.
And then what?
Advancing civilization...
Pursuing the arts...
Passing down genes...
Preserving the species...
What's the meaning of any of that?
"Love is eternal"? "Make memories"?
"The soul never dies"?
All this hope around intangible
ideas that have no guarantee!
What if humans go extinct, the Earth dies,
and it gets swallowed by the Sun,
and the universe comes to an end?
Whether you live or die, none of it matters!
He's insane...
Some say it's all about
living in the moment.
But that doesn't change the fact
that nothing matters.
Even murder is meaningless.
But look at all these people, mindlessly
looking for the value in futile things.
Humans are the worst with
their misguided intellect,
which is why I'm gonna kill 'em all off!
Everything's futile... So
he's fine murdering people?
You guys are gonna kill
the Emperor too, right?
It'd be convenient for me if you get to
them first, so I'll let you live for now.
There, I talked.
Now gimme Omi-kun!
Sane.
Here's a good hack. All you gotta do in
these situations is agree then ignore 'em!
Better run!
Wha?
Huh?
I got this. You guys go on without me...
I've always wanted to say that, you know!
Just lemme know how
to catch up with you later!
Okay. We'll take care of Omi,
so you better come back!
Let's go!
Sorry!
Later!
Make sure to tell the teacher
if you get a tummy ache!
You're not my mom!
You ruined the tension I created!
Never talk about how life
is meaningless in front of Sane.
You're not going anywhere.
I swear I'll protect those guys!
Oh, really?
Promise that you won't chase us,
inconvenience us,
or involve yourself with us
at all from now on.
Otherwise I'll kill you right here and now!
I've got a grasp on your Prime Right, dude.
He instantly split my blade
in two, which means...
The Scission Right under
the Transmutation Attribute.
Isn't that right?
Let's put it to the test.
I knew it!
As long I don't touch him...
Cool moves! What sports did you do?
Spring formation.
Fuse!
Separate!
Take this!
Oh, this thing?
There!
Dammit... How did he do that?!
So it's not the Scission Right?
Then what is it?!
See, get it now?
Mido wouldn't pair up with just anyone.
Mido's the brains, and I'm the guns.
So yeah, I guess I'm pretty strong.
Wanna know my Prime Right before you die?
Transmutation Attribute.
Prime Right of Division.
Division?!
Physical division, perceptive division,
qualitative division.
I can exercise division
within these three properties.
I split your blade with physical division.
I stopped the rubble
by dividing the existing space.
No more space, no more movement.
There are some exceptions,
but that's a secret!
How can I beat him...?
Now, don't let up like that.
Bye bye!
I won't make i—
Woah!
Hey, I wondered when I'd see
you again... to avenge Isshiki!
Hey there... You're that girl
who was with the Isshiki lady!
The name's Rika Suzuki.
Better remember that,
you decapitating psycho!
Weird... I thought I killed you
when you came back for Isshiki...
By crushing you with
the building like I just did now.
Sucks for you. You can't kill me.
I can avoid all physical harm
with my Prime Right of Evasion.
Any cause of harm can be totally evaded.
Same goes for him as long as he's with me.
Hmm... Then I guess I have
no way of killing you.
W-What are you doing here?
I was at City Hall when a guide popped up.
I followed the screen and here I am.
Screen?
Presentation Right! Gobo guided her!
I had to sacrifice my right leg as a risk...
Can't lie, I resented Isshiki for that.
But I'm alive now thanks to her.
Moreover... Isshiki was
a good person at heart.
I won't forgive you for killing her!
Umm, okay...? Congrats, I guess!
Ah?
Good for you for surviving! See ya!
I'm looking forward to you guys
killing the Emperor before me!
Then maybe you should give us
some more information, Iruga-kun.
Yagi-chan!
He's the one who tossed me over here!
Huh? Tossed?
Particularly, how to find
the Emperor's whereabouts,
how to defeat the Emperor, and
strategies surrounding Tasuketsu.
We could use these three
pieces of information.
Fine, then.
Bottom line, it's all pretty hit or miss.
I think the Emperor's in Tokyo, though.
All survivors are within the
23 wards, so you'd be right.
You knew and still asked? What a drag.
Not sure 'bout the right way
to beat the Emperor.
Prolly better to wait for an opening
and kill them instantly.
What else... Oh, right, Tasuketsu strategies.
Let's just say...
The key is to block tallies.
Tasuketsu can't take place without
submissions in the Second Stage, so...
If you keep a laptop and enter the password
each day to avoid recoveries...
Tasuketsu will not be held today
as questions were not accepted.
They can't hold Tasuketsu at all.
Either way, you'll need to get
your hands on a laptop first.
Why is he so confident?
...Of course!
With fewer restraints, there's
bound to be more competition.
Naturally, people will fight
those in possession of a laptop.
You're waiting for the moment they lose
ownership of their laptop, meaning...
Mido's Prime Right... it's the
Right of Succession, isn't it?
Aw, man! You figured it out...
Right you are!
We'll get a laptop that way, then keep it
without submitting any questions.
We don't wanna play into
the Emperor's hands, see?
What the hell does that mean?
Didn't you notice? Anyone can beat Tasuketsu
by asking 'who' was 'where' at 'what time'.
What good is Tasuketsu with
a gaping hole like that, huh?
Welp, you can figure out
the rest on your own.
I'm sure the fight over laptops will
balance out the population, anyway.
Didn't you say you wanna annihilate
the entire human race?
Why go about it in such a roundabout way?
You can't underestimate the Emperor.
Gotta play your hands carefully
or it's game over before you know it.
I'll just say the Rejection Right kid died.
I gave you all the hints you need.
You'll be able to figure it out
if you're smart.
Maybe ask for some help. Say...
from the smartest person you know.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
I guess I was right
to be cautious, after all.
Why are there people here in Nerima
when it's not even the Designated Area?
And one of them is Sudo?!
Just when I lost sight of Souma...
Congratulations, you've both been chosen!
Nice to meet you, I'm the Emperor.
W-What...?!
What a cheap lie.
Either he's given up by not heading to the
Designated Area or he has another motive.
Based on what he just said,
he's definitely toying with us.
This guy's a threat...
a difficult one, at that.
Get in my way and you'll die.
I'll kill you first.
Not bad.
I'm a black belt, you know.
Shinozaki... Sensei, I suppose...
Why are you in Nerima?
I was chasing Jin yesterday afternoon
when I was ordered by the Emperor...
to disengage and head to
Nerima Ward or be executed.
An order like that by
the Emperor? Impossible.
I was searching for somewhere safe
when I found this school.
So you ran out of fear and found
peace of mind at a school...
You're a teacher, after all.
I thought you were vile scum,
but I stand corrected.
You're not a bad person, just cowardly.
Your misguided choices came
from a genuine desire to survive.
Reconsider your options.
You may be alive like Narita and the
others, but they have each other.
Meanwhile, you're all alone.
I-I have my own—
Souma only helps me out of obligation...
So I'm alone...
Let me give you a piece of advice
in case you need it.
Work together with the others and
survive as a team until the end.
And if you still can't find a solution,
then you can betray them.
By that point, they'll be fighting
among the group, anyway.
No one would criticize you for anything.
You're telling me to rejoin
Narita and the others...?
Yes, if you're not genuinely a bad person.
There's no way they'd accept me now...
A stun grenade...!
Cover your eyes and ears!
You seem more intelligent. You die first.
Why you...!
Come at me!
I'll read your every move with my
Visualization Right and take you down!
I'm losing too much blood...
I don't have time.
He changed his target based on intelligence.
Could he have figured out
why I came to Nerima?
If so, then he must have the same idea...
Sudo! You alright?
We've got to stop the bleeding!
Idiot! Don't give him an opening!
We have to get to safety.
But your wound!
Thankfully... this is my arena.
A mic?
Cover your ears!
Don't take this personally,
but this is goodbye!
Go!
Now's our chance.
No matter. He won't make it
with that wound anyway.
How did you do that?
I placed an old radio cassette
player in a classroom.
Sound from the mic sets off
the meter for detonation.
I used fire powder commonly
carried by magicians.
Magicians?
I got it from an old friend
with eccentric hobbies.
But never mind that.
I need to tell you something.
Go to this school's library.
You'll find notes I've collected
on Tasuketsu.
That should tell you...
where the Emperor is...
Get that... to the others...
That's enough talking!
We've got to treat you first!
Ryohei.
Ryohei, look at the sky.
Did you hear about Sudo-san's accident?
Yeah, the older child was with him, too.
Poor thing...
That's the same sky your father and Kohei saw.
There will always be a sky above you.
As long as it's there,
we'll be connected forever.
That day, the sky was so blue and bright.
It pierced my heart and
filled it with color and light.
I wanted to help Mom live comfortably
on behalf of my dad and brother.
So I did everything I could to get ahead.
Sugishin Prep School
And I joined a prep school
we couldn't afford.
That was where I met...
May 4   Mock Exam Results
First Place   Tojuro Yagihashi   500 points
Second Place    Ryohei Sudo    495 points
Third Place    Amelia Yamada    456 points
Fourth Place    Toru Sasaoka    402 points
May 21    Mock Exam Results
First Place   Tojuro Yagihashi   500 points
Second Place    Ryohei Sudo    497 points
Third Place    Amelia Yamada    451 points
Fourth Place    Yudai Abe    392 points
Yagihashi! Who do you think you are?!
What's the matter?
Tuition fees! I heard you paid mine off!
Do you feel sorry for me? Am I supposed
to be grateful for your help?!
A fortune teller told me the other day...
Unless I pay your tuition fees,
my parents will explode.
Stop making fun of me!
I should say the same.
Who's smarter here―you or me?
Do you really think your answer
would be better than mine?
I'll tell you what I figured out.
They would explode.
I arrived at that conclusion with
this intelligent brain of mine.
It's gotta be right.
Green onion?
Yagihashi...! Poking fun at me again!
Ryohei, that's enough.
You need to quit studying.
Mom, but...!
When was the last time I talked
with Mom face to face like this...?
It's all my fault. It was supposed to be
all for her, but instead I...
Yagihashi? What are you doing here?
Did the green onion work?
Huh? Green onion?
Of course. So you knew
this would happen all along.
You really got me.
Green onions are good for colds.
You have to keep it on you
for it to work, though.
You sure have an odd way of lending a hand.
Were the tuition fees just
a way to talk to me?
That's only half the reason.
I happen to admire your work ethic.
As your rival and admirer, I want
to see you perform your best.
My family and I are actually
moving to Saitama soon.
So I want to propose a friendly competition.
One that involves our grades.
Whoever ranks higher in the nationwide
mock exam when we enter high school wins.
So the tuition was my entry fee...
Fine, I'm in.
It's a deal, then.
You really were the one in first place.
No wonder I always came in second.
Thank you, Yagihashi.
You gave me the strength
to be my best for Mom.
I'll make her happy... for my dad
and brother's sake. No matter what.
Two left
You are currently looking at this screen
Congratulations.
You are all alive by chance.
Nice to meet you. I'm the Emperor.
I wonder why?
Here I am, defeated midway.
Yet my heart feels like
it's been filled with light.
Oh, that's right... The sky...
It's the same sky...
Nearby
from that day.